Hey guys welcome back to my mini vlog.  So today
's mini vlog is very special because we were
going to the market for shopping.  So look,
here Di's vlogging also started and Arwa
Jaan was doing hi and this poor girl got into a
bad condition in the car.  He doesn't know
what happens.  It feels like vomiting.
So there was a lot of traffic here.  Then
finally [music] we arrived and here Pe Di
and I were talking about something.  So Di was
laughing at that very thing.  So finally we went to
Gandhinagar Apsara Road.  You know that a
very good collection is available here in Jammu.
We were also thinking the same thing this time
[music] too because last year there was a
very good collection.  So we also went there with that thought in mind.
Who knows, it might happen this time too.  But whether
we got that good collection this time or not.
You will get to see that in the full vlog.  So
here Didi was trying this which was very
cute to me and Didi too.  And
look, I bought this suit
at first sight because its stuff was very
soft and it was a very cute suit.
So finally we took this one too.  Then we went to
see the purse because Didi had to buy a purse.
He hasn't taken it for a long time.  Then we
finally bought two-three from there, which were a lot.
So after that we went to Joe's to do
some shopping [music] because
we couldn't find what we wanted there.  So
finally we went there.  Then we came
here to eat something because
we had left in the morning.  I was so hungry, so very
much.  So we are going home now.  Thanks
for watching.